Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0643 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0643)
      Guest: Jo Anne Birnie Danzker
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0644 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0644)
      Original Format: HHB DAT
      Original Number: 2001-04
      Saadia: Women of the Moroccan Resistance
      Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0645 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0645)
      Original Number: 2001-05
      Ex Voto Odo Ya! Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0646 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0646)
      Original Number: 2001-06
      Crazy Guest: Heddy Honigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 2001; ID: 326.0647 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0647)
      Original Number: 2001-07
      Obon, Origin, Heartbeat
      Guest: Andrej Zdravic
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 18, 2001; ID: 326.0648 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0648)
      Original Number: 2001-08
      Brave New Land, Guest: Lucia Murat
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 2001; ID: 326.0649 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0649)
      Original Number: 2001-09
      The Underground Orchestra, Guest: Heddy Honigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 2001; ID: 326.0650 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0650)
      Original Number: 2001-10
      My Grandmother's Camera, Guest: Tania Cypriano
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 2001; ID: 326.0651 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0651)
      Original Number: 2001-11
      Metal and Melancholy, Guest: Heddy Henigmann
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 2001; ID: 326.0652 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0652)
      Original Number: 2001-12
      Fast Runner, Guest: Norm Cohen
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 2001; ID: 326.0653 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0653)
      Original Number: 2001-13
      Seers and Clowns, Africa, Witch Madness, Our Spirited Earth, W.O.W.
      Way to Father's Village
      Faith Hubley, Richard Funy
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 2001; ID: 326.0654 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0654)
      Original Number: 2001-14
      Pigeon Within, One Self: Fish Girl, Blue Vinyl,
      Guests: Emily Hobley, Judith Helfand, Dan Gold
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 2001; ID: 326.0655 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0655)
      Original Number: 2001-15
      Guests: Emily Hobley, Judith Helfrand, Dan Gold
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 2001; ID: 326.0656 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0656)
      Original Number: 2001-16
      Delivery Man, Blake Ball, Excerpt from Hedwig & the Angry Itch and Death by Design
      Emily Hobley
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 2001; ID: 326.0657 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0657)
      Original Number: 2001-17
      Breath Puddles [Phenix] Guest: Andrej Zdravic
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 2001; ID: 326.0658 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0658)
      Original Number: 2001-18
      Dirty Laundry Sea in the Blood
      Richard Fong
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 2001; ID: 326.0659 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0659)
      Original Number: 2001-19
      Independent Spirits, Her Grandmother's Gift, My Universe Inside Out,
      Guests: Sybil de Guardia, Patty Wineapple, Emily Hobley, Faith Hobley
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, 2001; ID: 326.0660 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0660)
      Original Number: 2001-20
      Threat
      Guests: Norm Cohen Carl Svenstedt
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 2001; ID: 326.0661 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0661)
      Original Format: Quantegy DAT
      Original Number: 2001-21
      End of discussion with Carl & Norm
      Wrap up discussion
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, 2001; ID: 326.0662 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0662)
      Original Number: 2001-22
      Hubley Interview with Tarik
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 14, 2002; ID: 326.0663 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0663)
      Original Number: 2002-01
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0664 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0664)
      Original Number: 2002-02
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0665 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0665)
      Original Number: 2002-03
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Uman Discussion Tape, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0666 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0666)
      Naomi Uman Discussion
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 15, 2002; ID: 326.0667 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0667)
      Original Number: 2002-04
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0668 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0668)
      Original Number: 2002-05
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0669 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0669)
      Original Number: 2002-06
      Title: A Burning Star, Guest: Kenji Onishi, Moderator: Ed Halter, Recordist: Juan Castito
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0670 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0670)
      Original Number: 2002-07
      Title: A Burning Star Guest: Kenji Onishi Moderator: Ed Halter Recordist: Juan Casteto
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 16, 2002; ID: 326.0671 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0671)
      Original Number: 2002-08
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 17, 2002; ID: 326.0672 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0672)
      Original Number: 2002-09
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Anger Tape, June 17, 2002; ID: 326.0673 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0673)
      Kenneth Anger
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 2002; ID: 326.0674 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0674)
      Original Number: 2002-10
      Fotopoulos/Oshina Shorts
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 18, 2002; ID: 326.0675 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0675)
      Original Number: 2002-11
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 18, 2002; ID: 326.0676 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0676)
      Original Number: 2002-12
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 19, 2002; ID: 326.0677 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0677)
      Original Number: 2002-13
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 19, 2002; ID: 326.0678 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0678)
      Original Number: 2002-14
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, 2002; ID: 326.0679 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0679)
      Original Number: 2002-15
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 2002; ID: 326.0680 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0680)
      Original Number: 2002-16
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 20, 2002; ID: 326.0681 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0681)
      Original Number: 2002-17
      Hitler's Hat - Jeff Kruwk
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 20, 2002; ID: 326.0682 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0682)
      Original Number: 2002-18
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - June 21st A.M., June 21, 2002; ID: 326.0683 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0683)
    - 48th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Unmarked, 2002; ID: 326.0684 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0684)
      Discussion following Hitler's Hat with J. Krulik Moderator: Ed
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 14, 2003; ID: 326.0685 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0685)
      Original Number: 2003-01
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 15, 2003; ID: 326.0686 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0686)
      Original Number: 2003-02
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 15, 2003; ID: 326.0687 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0687)
      Original Number: 2003-03
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 2003; ID: 326.0688 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0688)
      Original Number: 2003-04
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0689 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0689)
      Original Number: 2003-05
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0690 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0690)
      Original Number: 2003-06
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0691 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0691)
      Original Number: 2003-07
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 16, 2003; ID: 326.0692 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0692)
      Original Number: 2003-08
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 17, 2003; ID: 326.0693 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0693)
      Original Number: 2003-09
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 17, 2003; ID: 326.0694 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0694)
      Original Number: 2003-10
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0695 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0695)
      Original Number: 2003-11
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0696 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0696)
      Original Number: 2003-12
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 18, 2003; ID: 326.0697 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0697)
      Original Number: 2003-13
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0698 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0698)
      Original Number: 2003-14
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0699 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0699)
      Original Number: 2003-15
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 20, 2003; ID: 326.0700 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0700)
      Original Number: 2003-16
    - 49th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 19, 2003; ID: 326.0701 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0701)
      Original Number: 2003-17
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0702 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0702)
      Original Number: 001
      Jennifer Reeves, Robert Breer, Janie Geiser, Peter Hutton, Phil Solomon
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0703 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0703)
      Original Number: 002
      What Mozart Saw - Burkhardt/Cornell
      Killer of Sheep - C. Burnett
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 13, 2004; ID: 326.0704 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0704)
      TRT: 00:05:00
      Original Number: 003
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 14, 2004; ID: 326.0705 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0705)
      TRT: 01:55:20
      Original Number: 005
      Moderator: William Sloan, Ricky Leacock, Michel Braulf
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8A, June 15, 2004; ID: 326.0706 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0706)
      Original Number: 008 A
      Pancho Villa, Director's Commentary and life [Buitar]
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8B, 2004; ID: 326.0707 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0707)
      Original Number: 008 B
      Guests: Gregario Raha, Andreas Guarim
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 15, 2004; ID: 326.0708 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0708)
      Original Number: 009
      10th Flaherty Seminar, Guest: Jennifer Reeves Programmer: Susan Oxtoby
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 16, 2004; ID: 326.0709 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0709)
      Original Number: 010
      Wednesday June 16, 2004 Afternoon Program by Ruth Brodey and Louis Massiah
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0710 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0710)
      Original Number: 011
      10th Flaherty Seminar Guest: Morgan Fisher Lewis Klahr
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 16, 2004; ID: 326.0711 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0711)
      Original Number: 012
      Superbia; Journeys; Themes; Short Fuse
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0712 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0712)
      Original Number: 013
      Media Activism and Public Access 50th Flaherty Seminar Guests: Dede Hallek George Stoney
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 17, 2004; ID: 326.0713 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0713)
      Original Number: 014
      The 50th Flaherty Programmer: Susan Octoby Artists: Peter Hutton and Ulrike Ottinger
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 18, 2004; ID: 326.0714 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0714)
      Original Number: 015
      The 50th Flaherty Seminar "The Cod World" by Shirley Clarke Moderator: Deedee Halleck
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, [undated]; ID: 326.0715 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0715)
      Original Number: 016
      The 50th Flaherty Seminar discussion session about "Southeast passage: A journey to the new blank spots on the map of Europe" (Part I) Guest: Ulrike Ottinger (Director)
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, [undated]; ID: 326.0716 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0716)
      Original Number: 017
      50th Flaherty Seminar George Stoney "getting out"
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 18, 2004; ID: 326.0717 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0717)
      Original Number: 018
      50th Flaherty Seminar Louise Bourque Morgan Fischer
    - 50th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, [undated]; ID: 326.0718 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0718)
      Original Number: 019
      50th Flaherty Seminar Guest: Clive Holden Film: "Trains of Winnipeg" Programmer: Susan Oxtoby
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, June 11, 2005; ID: 326.0719 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0719)
      Original Format: Audiocassette
      Original Number: 2005-01
      Opening Comments
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 02, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0720 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0720)
      Original Number: 2005-02
      Discussion 2-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 03, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0721 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0721)
      Original Number: 2005-03
      Discussion 2-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 04, June 12, 2005; ID: 326.0722 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0722)
      Original Number: 2005-04
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 05, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0723 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0723)
      Original Number: 2005-05
      Discussion 3-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 06, [undated]; ID: 326.0724 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0724)
      Original Number: 2005-06
      Leandro Katz slide show
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 07, [undated]; ID: 326.0725 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0725)
      Original Number: 2005-07
      Discussion 3-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 08, March 3, 2005; ID: 326.0726 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0726)
      Original Number: 2005-08
      6B Discussion 3B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 09, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0727 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0727)
      Original Number: 2005-09
      Discussion 3A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 13, 2005; ID: 326.0728 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0728)
      Original Number: 2005-10
      7B Discussion 3-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0729 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0729)
      Original Number: 2005-11
      Discussion 4-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0730 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0730)
      Original Number: 2005-12
      Discussion 4-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0731 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0731)
      Original Number: 2005-13
      Discussion 4-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 14, 2005; ID: 326.0732 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0732)
      Original Number: 2005-14
      Discussion 4-D
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 15, 2005; ID: 326.0733 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0733)
      Original Number: 2005-15
      Discussion 5-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 15, 2005; ID: 326.0734 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0734)
      Original Number: 2005-16
      Discussion 5-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0735 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0735)
      Original Number: 2005-17
      Discussion 6-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0736 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0736)
      Original Number: 2005-18
      Discussion 6-B
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, June 16, 2005; ID: 326.0737 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0737)
      Original Number: 2005-19
      Discussion 6-C
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, June 18, 2005; ID: 326.0738 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0738)
      Original Number: 2005-20
      Discussion 8-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, June 17, 2005; ID: 326.0739 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0739)
      Original Number: 2005-21
      Discussion 7-A
    - 51st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, June 17, 2005; ID: 326.0740 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0740)
      Original Number: 2005-22
      Discussion 7-B
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, June 17, 2006; ID: 326.0741 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0741)
      Original Format: DAT
      Original Number: 2006-01
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 02, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0742 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0742)
      Original Number: 2006-02
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 03, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0743 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0743)
      Original Number: 2006-03
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 04, June 18, 2006; ID: 326. 0743 (Box 15, Media ID: 326. 0743)
      Original Number: 2006-04
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 05, June 18, 2006; ID: 326.0745 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0745)
      Original Number: 2006-05
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 06, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0746 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0746)
      Original Number: 2006-06
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 07, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0747 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0747)
      Original Number: 2006-07
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 08, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0748 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0748)
      Original Number: 2006-08
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 09, June 19, 2006; ID: 326.0749 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0749)
      Original Number: 2006-09
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0750 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0750)
      Original Number: 2006-10
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0751 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0751)
      Original Number: 2006-11
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 20, 2006; ID: 326.0752 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0752)
      Original Number: 2006-12
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 2006; ID: 326.0753 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0753)
      Original Number: 2006-13
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 2006; ID: 326.0754 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0754)
      Original Number: 2006-14
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 21, 2006; ID: 326.0755 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0755)
      Original Number: 2006-15
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0756 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0756)
      Original Number: 2006-16
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0757 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0757)
      Original Number: 2006-17
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 2006; ID: 326.0758 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0758)
      Original Number: 2006-18
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0759 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0759)
      Original Number: 2006-19
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, June 22, 2006; ID: 326.0760 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0760)
      Original Number: 2006-20
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, June 23, 2006; ID: 326.0761 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0761)
      Original Number: 2006-23
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, June 23, 2006; ID: 326.0762 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0762)
      Original Number: 2006-22
    - 52nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 23, June 24, 2006; ID: 326.0764 (Box 15, Media ID: 326.0764)
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 2007; ID: 326.0764 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0764)
      Original Number: 2007-01
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 17, 2007; ID: 326.0765 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0765)
      Original Number: 2007-02
      Moderator: Margarita de la Vega-Hurtado, Panelists: Osvalde Lewat-Hallade, Natalie Almada
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 17, 2007; ID: 326.0766 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0766)
      Original Number: 2007-03
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 18, 2007; ID: 326.0767 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0767)
      Original Number: 2007-04
      Filmmakers: N. Almada, L.R. Helmrich
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 18, 2007; ID: 326.0768 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0768)
      Original Number: 2007-05
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 18, 2007; ID: 326.0769 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0769)
      Original Number: 2007-06
      Filmmakers: N. Almada, L.R. Heimrich
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 18, 2007; ID: 326.0770 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0770)
      Original Number: 2007-07
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 19, 2007; ID: 326.0771 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0771)
      Original Number: 2007-08
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 19, 2007; ID: 326.0772 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0772)
      Original Number: 2007-09
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 20, 2007; ID: 326.0773 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0773)
      Original Number: 2007-11
      Moderator: Ed Halter, Panelists: Juan Carlos Zaldivar, Osvalde Lewat-Hallade
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 20, 2007; ID: 326.0774 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0774)
      Original Number: 2007-12
      - "Africanized" Theo Eshetu
      - "Dry Season" Haroun
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13-1, June 21, 2007; ID: 326.0775 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0775)
      Original Number: 2007-13-1
      Theo Eshetu, Natalia Almado
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13-2, June 21, 2007; ID: 326.0776 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0776)
      Original Number: 2007-13-2
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 21, 2007; ID: 326.0777 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0777)
      Original Number: 2007-14
      Bevanda - osvalde lewat-hallade, Khalo Matabane
    - 53rd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 21, 2007; ID: 326.0778 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0778)
      Original Number: 2007-15
      Natalia Almada
    - 54th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 1, 2008; ID: 326.0779 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0779)
      Original Format: DVD-R (audio MP3 file)
      Original Number: 2008
    - 55th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 1, 2009; ID: 326.0780 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0780)
      Original Format: DVD-R
      Original Number: 2009
    - 56th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 1, June 19, 2010; ID: 326.0781 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0781)
      Original Format: DVD-R (audio wave file)
      Original Number: 2010-01
    - 54th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 2, June 22, 2010; ID: 326.0782 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0782)
      Original Number: 2010-02
    - 54th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 3, June 24, 2010; ID: 326.0783 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0783)
      Original Number: 2010-03
    - 55th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 1, June 18, 2011; ID: 326.0784 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0784)
      Original Number: 2011-01
    - 55th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 2, June 20, 2011; ID: 326.0785 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0785)
      Original Number: 2011-02
    - 55th Annual Flaherty Seminar - DVD 3, June 22, 2011; ID: 326.0786 (Box 16, Media ID: 326.0786)
      Original Number: 2011-03
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings
    - Digital Flaherty Session 1 - Stationary Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0787 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0787)
      Original Format: Mini-DV
      Original Number:
      Dee Dee Halleck, Amy Goodman, Jacquie Soshen, Igor Vamos
    - Digital Flaherty Session 1 - Stationary Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0788 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0788)
    - Digital Flaherty Session 1 - Mobile Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0789 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0789)
      Currently Unknown
    - Digital Flaherty Session 1 - Mobile Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0790 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0790)
      Currently Unknown.
    - Digital Flaherty Session 2 - Mobile Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0791 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0791)
      Alex Rivera
    - Digital Flaherty Session 2 - Stationary Camera, unknown; ID: 326.0792 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0792)
    - Digital Flaherty Session 3 - Stationary Camera, November 17th; ID: 326.0793 (Box 17, Media ID: 326.0793)